stardriftempires.com 2017-06-06

# Stardrift Empires

Last Updated 2011/08/09

**BLUE FROG GAMING, INC.**

**Privacy Policy**

Welcome, and thank you for your interest in Blue Frog Gaming, Inc. (“Blue Frog”), and the Service, as described in the Blue Frog Gaming, Inc. Terms of Use. This Privacy Policy describes what information we gather from you, how we use and disclose that information, and what we do to protect it. By using the Service, you expressly consent to the information handling practices described in this policy. 

This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and is subject to the Blue Frog Terms of Use. The practices described in this policy apply only to Blue Frog’s use of information supplied by you to Blue Frog through the Service. Information collected from you by others, such as third party web sites that you access through links on the Service, may also be governed by those entities’ privacy policies.

**The Information Blue Frog Collects:**

**User-Provided Information:** You may provide to Blue Frog what is generally called “personally identifiable” information (such as your email address, age, zip code, credit card number and billing information) when using the Service, such as when you register, use the Apps, or purchase virtual goods. If you use the Service with your mobile device, we may also have access to your device ID or phone number. 

**“Cookies” Information:** When you use the Service, we may send one or more cookies – small text files containing a string of alphanumeric characters – to your computer. Blue Frog may use both session cookies and persistent cookies. A session cookie disappears after you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser and may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the Service. Persistent cookies can be removed. Please review your web browser “Help” file to learn the proper way to modify your cookie settings. Please note that if you delete, or choose not to accept, cookies from the Service, you may not be able to utilize the features of the Service to their fullest potential.

**“Automatically Collected” Information:** When you use the Service or open one of our HTML emails, we may automatically record certain information from your web browser by using different types of technology, including “clear gifs” or “web beacons.” This “automatically collected” information may include Internet Protocol address (“IP Address”) or other device address or ID, web browser and/or device type, the web pages or sites that you visit just before or just after the Service, the pages you view on the Service, and the dates and times that you visit, access, or use the Service. 

**Information from Other Sources:** We may also obtain information, including personally identifiable information, from third parties and sources other than the Service, such as other users who send messages to you through the Service, or third party service providers who you use to access features of the Service, such as purchasing in-game virtual goods. By using Apps offered by Blue Frog on Facebook, Blue Frog will have access to your Facebook profile information that your Facebook privacy settings are configured to expose to Facebook apps, and user activity within some Facebook applications. If we combine or associate information from other sources with personally identifiable information that we collect through the Service, we will treat the combined information as personally identifiable information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

**The Way Blue Frog Uses Information:**

Blue Frog uses the information you provide or that we collect to operate, maintain, enhance, and provide all of the features and services found on the Service. We will use your email address to contact you for administrative purposes, for game-related communications, for customer service purposes, to address intellectual property infringement, rights of privacy, or defamation issues, or any regarding content that you have posted to the Service. You may not opt out of such communications. We may also use your email address to let you know about new features, games, or promotional offers on the Service. You may configure the nature and frequency of these messages or opt out of such messages through the Service.

Blue Frog may use the information you provide to process credit card payments for the Service through our Blue Frog Pay payment system. We only use your credit card information and address to process payments you have made and do not retain such information on our systems. 

Blue Frog uses all of the information that you provide or that we collect and/or aggregate to understand and analyze the usage trends, interests, and preferences of our users, to improve the way the Service works and looks, and to create new features and functionality.

Content on the Blue Frog Site and Service, may include relevant advertisements which may be selected based in part on your demographic information, interests, preferences, and usage patterns within the Service. Blue Frog may use “automatically collected” information and “cookies” information to: (a) personalize our services, such as remembering your information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit the Service; (b) provide customized third party advertisements, content, and information; (c) monitor and analyze the effectiveness of Blue Frog and third party marketing activities; (d) monitor aggregate usage metrics such as total number of visitors, pages viewed, Apps accessed, etc.; and (e) track your entries, submissions, and status in any promotions or other activities. 

Blue Frog may allow you to import your email contacts from third party email providers to allow you to communicate with your contacts within the Apps of the Service. The import process is handled by your email service and not by Blue Frog. We do not have access to any information stored in your email account other than email contacts that you provide to us and we do not store or have access to your user name and password for your email service.

Blue Frog may use your email address or other personally identifiable information to send promotional email related to services or products we think you may be interested in. You will have the ability to opt-out of receiving any such communications, either through links provided in the messages, or by updating your account preferences through the Service. 

**When Blue Frog Discloses Information:**

Your privacy is very important to us, and we are not in the business of selling your information. We do, however, disclose your personal information in a variety of circumstances.

The Service enables users to communicate in a variety of ways, including through our online game forums. Any personally identifiable information that you voluntarily choose to include in a message to another user, or in a publicly accessible area on the Service, such as a public profile page, or through posting User Content, will be available to other users who access that content. Once you make your personally identifiable information available in this way, it may be collected and used by the recipients without restriction beyond our control. 

Blue Frog makes certain automatically collected and other aggregate non-personally-identifiable information available to third parties, to: (i) comply with various reporting obligations; (ii) for business or marketing purposes; or (iii) to assist such parties in understanding our users’ interests, habits, and usage patterns for certain programs, content, services, advertisements, promotions, and/or functionality available through the Service. 

Blue Frog works with third party partners to develop, distribute, and publish cobranded games. For cobranded games in particular, Blue Frog may make your personal information available to the third party partner, subject to the terms of that third party partner’s privacy policy which contains restrictions on use and disclosure generally comparable with our privacy policy. 

Blue Frog works with third party service providers to provide website, application development, hosting, and maintenance, payment processing, as well as other services for us. To the extent it is necessary for these service providers to complete their contractual obligations to Blue Frog, these third parties may have access to or process your personally identifiable information. These disclosures are made under terms generally comparable to this policy, and the recipients are limited to using the information the purpose for which it was provided and to protect the information as we would.

Blue Frog may also disclose your information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with state and federal laws (such as U.S. Copyright law), in response to a court order, judicial or other government subpoena or warrant, or to otherwise cooperate with law enforcement activity. 

Blue Frog also reserves the right to disclose your information that we believe, in good faith, is appropriate or necessary to take precautions against liability; to protect Blue Frog and others from fraudulent, abusive, or unlawful uses or activity; to investigate and defend ourselves against any third party claims or allegations; to assist government enforcement agencies; to protect the security or integrity of the Service; or to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Blue Frog, our users, or others.

**Your Choices:**

You may, of course, decline to share certain personally identifiable information with Blue Frog, in which case Blue Frog may not be able to provide to you some of the features and functionality found on the Service. You may update, correct, or delete your profile information and preferences at any time by accessing your account preferences page through the Service. Please note that while your changes may be reflected promptly in active user databases, we may retain all information you submit for a variety of purposes, including backups and archiving, prevention of fraud and abuse, and analytics.

To protect your privacy and security, we take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting you account access or making corrections to your information. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your unique password and account information at all times. 

**Third Party Services:**

The Service contains links to Web sites and services provided by third parties. Any personally identifiable information you provide on third party sites or services is provided directly to that third party and is subject to that third party’s policies governing privacy and security. We are not responsible for the content or privacy and security practices and policies of third party sites or services to which links are displayed on the Service. We encourage you to learn about third parties’ privacy and security policies before providing them with personally identifiable information.

**Our Commitment to Children’s Privacy:**

Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. For that reason, Blue Frog does not knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information from persons under 13 years-of-age, and no part of the Service is directed to persons under 13\. If you are under 13 years of age, then please do not use or access THE SERVICE at any time or in any manner. If Blue Frog learns that personally identifiable information of children under the age of 13 has been collected on the Service without verifiable parental consent, then Blue Frog will take the appropriate steps to delete this information. If you are a parent or guardian and discover that your child under the age of 13 has obtained an account on the Service, then you may alert Blue Frog at privacy@bluefroggaming.com and request that Blue Frog delete that child’s personal information from its systems. 

**Our Commitment to Data Security:**

Blue Frog uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to Blue Frog, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission of information, Blue Frog makes commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of our systems. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards. 

If Blue Frog learns of a security systems breach, then we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. Blue Frog may post a notice through the Service if a security breach occurs. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing. Irrespective of where you live, if you would like to receive a free written notice of a security breach you should notify us at privacy@bluefroggaming.com.

**International Visitors:**

The Service is hosted in the United States and is intended solely for visitors located within the United States. If you nonetheless choose to use the Service from the European Union or other regions of the world with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from U.S. law, then please note that you are transferring your personally identifiable information outside of those regions to the United States and by providing your personally identifiable information on the Service you consent to that transfer.

**In the Event of Merger or Sale:**

In the event that all or a portion of Blue Frog or its assets is acquired by or merged with a third party entity, we reserve the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the information that we have collected from users in connection with such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control.

**Changes and Updates to this Privacy Policy:**

Please revisit this page periodically to stay aware of any changes to this Privacy Policy, which may be revised periodically at Blue Frog’ sole discretion, as provided in Section 8 of the Blue Frog Terms of Use. If we modify the Privacy Policy, we will make it available through the Service, and indicate the date of the latest revision. In the event that the modifications materially alter your rights or obligations hereunder we will make reasonable efforts to notify you of the change. For example, we may send a message to your email address, if we have one on file, or generate a pop-up or similar notification when you access the Service for the first time after such material changes are made. Our amended Privacy Policy will automatically take effect thirty days after it is made available through the Service, except that (i) we generally only use your personal information in the manner described in the Privacy Policy in effect when we received that personal information and (ii) if you do not agree with any changes to the Privacy Policy, you may terminate your account ceasing use of the Service. Your continued use of the Service after revised Privacy Policy has become effective indicates that you have read, understood and agreed to the current version of the Privacy Policy.

**Blue Frog Contact Information:**

Please contact Blue Frog with any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, your personal information, our third party disclosure practices, or your consent choices by email: privacy@bluefroggaming.com.
